你就幫我看守家裡
Just hold down the fort for me
就離開，半個月，或四週
I'll be gone for two weeks, or a month
一趟暑假，就爬一棵樹
Spent my summer climbing a tree
在上頭，有好多，可以看
there's so much to be seen from the top
直到墜落
Unless you fall
我也知道，你很怕高
And I know you're scared of heights
但沒關係，你知道你會飛
and it's okay, you know you can fly
但那墜落的想法只讓你淚落
But the thought of falling makes you want to cry
你又，怎麼不給，我們訊息回覆？
And why don't you respond to our texts?
我說，你有個愛你的家庭
You know, you have a family that loves you
那當你回家，來
So when you come home, let's
來一起回 Six Flags⁽¹⁾
let's go back to Six Flags
我贏了新的金魚，放在魚缸裡
I got new goldfish to put in the tank
我還可能餵呢
and I might just feed them
在你人生的這回
This time of your life
你聽來，家為何？
What sounds like home to you?
在太遲之前
Before it's too late
告訴我你愛我，你想我
tell me that you love and you miss me
你看來好棒
You look so great
但你感覺好像要死掉
but you feel like you're gonna die
在你人生的這回
This time of your life